GASTON NAHUEL PONCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

🗣 Buenos Aires, Argentina I 🛕 NahuelG.Ponce@gmail.com I 🐚 /gastonponce I 🐛 +54 9 11 3766-9897

Experience in FrontEnd development and I have worked in roles such as QA and Product Owner. Quick adaptation to new projects, challenges and technologies that the position requires. Work under pressure in leadership positions justifying and negotiating timelines with stakeholders.

EXPERIENCIA PROFESIONAL

Product Owner | Agrology Data S.R.L.

October 2022 - Presente

- API testing with Postman and documentation for integration with external systems.
- · Automated testing with Playwright.
- Hotjar survey for future improvements.
- Sprint planning, planning organization and progress presentation to the board of directors.
- Design screens with Figma and layout them using React, ReactComponent, HTML, CSS and JS.

FrontEnd - QA Analyst | ELDAR

January 2022 - October 2022

- Testing APIs with Postman and third-party API documentation for integrations.
- Surveying, analyzing proposals. Creating technical and functional documentation focused on financial transactions.
- Planning sprints and organizing planning.
- Designing, improving and testing Web and Android projects focused on facilitating financial transactions using Figma, HTML, CSS.

Analyst FrontEnd Angular | Mobile-I-Business

July 2020 - January 2022

- FrontEnd Layout of ABM's
 - · FormsModule, Routing, NgRx, Comunicación Módulos-Componentes
 - Maguetado con AngularMaterial, Flexbox, bootstrap, HTML/CSS
 - Integración con servicios de endpoint de backend
- · Reports, queries and StoredProcedure in T-SQL
- Bug reporting and tracking and root cause documentation.
- Building KPIs in Google DataStudio for product usability.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Information Systems

March 2021 - Present

Universidad Nacional de Lanús

- Object Oriented Programming: Paradigm theory, Java, DB connection, Hibernate, Springboot and Security, Building put, post, delete and get APIs in Java
- Relational databases: construction, normalization, maintenance.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Languages: Spanish (Native), English (Basic/Technical)
- Certifications / Courses: Fundamentos de Programación con SQL Server 2019 [Udemy] MS SQL Server 2019. Programación de Bases de Datos con T-SQL [EducacionIT] • HTML5 - JAVA - Hibernate - SQL Lite [#YoProgramo Argentina] • Angular: De cero a experto [UDEMY]